{
    "subject": "resource/We're_All_Gonna_Die",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "We're All Gonna Die is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.786008358001709,
            "question": "Where is We're All Gonna Die from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6744691729545593,
            "question": "When was We're All Gonna Die formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6735804677009583,
            "question": "Who are the members of We're All Gonna Die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6640453934669495,
            "question": "What country is associated with We're All Gonna Die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5688583850860596,
            "question": "What is the meaning behind the name 'We're All Gonna Die'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5280338525772095,
            "question": "Has We're All Gonna Die won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.420841783285141,
            "question": "Is We're All Gonna Die a band or a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.407396525144577,
            "question": "Are there any similar artists or bands to We're All Gonna Die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3266758620738983,
            "question": "Are there any famous albums or songs by We're All Gonna Die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32168540358543396,
            "question": "What genre of music might We're All Gonna Die create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=We're All Gonna Die is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9154_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous albums or songs by We're All Gonna Die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9154_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similar artists or bands to We're All Gonna Die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9154_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is We're All Gonna Die a band or a movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9154_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9154_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason is that none of the documents provided information about the country of origin for the movie/TV show/game/book \"We're All Gonna Die\". The files appear to be reviews, descriptions, or citations related to different forms of media with this title, but they do not mention anything about its country of origin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that \"We're All Gonna Die\" has had a premiere at SXSW (South by Southwest) in 2024, which is an event held in the United States. Therefore, it can be reasonably inferred that the show or movie originates from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided to suggest that \"We're All Gonna Die\" (either the docuseries, film, board game, or song) is from the United States.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that explicitly states or implies the country of origin for \"We're All Gonna Die\" (in any of its forms - docuseries, film, board game, song).",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no explicit information about the country of origin of \"We're All Gonna Die\", but Season 2 is mentioned as part of a docuseries, which suggests that it might be from Canada (where Jay Baruchel is based) rather than the United States.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}